(Sheldon:)Here's the problem with teleportation.
(Leonard:)Lay it on me.
Assuming a device could be invented...
...which would identify the state of matter
of an individual in one location...
...and transmit that to a distant location
for reassembly...
...you wouldn't have
transported the individual...
(Sheldon:)...you would have destroyed him in one
location and re-created him in another.
(Leonard:)How about that.
(Sheldon:)I would never use a transporter.
(Sheldon:)The original Sheldon
would have to be disintegrated...
(Sheldon:)...in order to create a new Sheldon.
(Leonard:)Would the new Sheldon be in any way
an improvement on the old Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)No, he would be exactly the same.
(Leonard:)That is a problem.
So you see it too?
(Dr Gablehouser(arriving):)Dr. Hofstadter, Dr. Cooper.
BOTH:
Dr. Gablehauser.
(Gablehouser:)Gentlemen,
I'd like you to meet Dennis Kim.
Dennis is a highly sought-after
doctoral candidate.